Correctional Association of New York; Records apap014
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Subject Files, 1947-1988; 1970-1985; 7; 11 cubic ft.
  - Lasker Decision - House of Detention for Men, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Law and Disorder, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Legal Aid Society, 1968-1973 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Legal Aid Society, 1968-1973 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Legal Issues of Female Inmates: A Report, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Legal Situation on Jailing Alcoholics for Public Intoxication in the United States, 1967 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Legal Status of Alcoholics - Social Welfare Implications, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Legislation - NYS: 1973 Session, 1973-1974 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Liman Commission, 1982; 2 folders (Box 5, Folder 16-17)
  - Long Island Correctional Facility - Closure, 1983-1984 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Man on the Periphery, 1964 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Mandatory Sentences in Drug Cases, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Marijuana, 1968-1970 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Marshaling Citizen Power to Modernize Corrections, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Massachusetts, 1980-1987 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Media, 1980-1987 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Methadone Program, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Minimum Standards of Civil and Human Rights for Inmates in Correctional Institutions, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Minnesota, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Minnesota Community Corrections Act Evaluation, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Miscellaneous, 1981-1987 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Model Residential Juvenile Sex-offender Treatment Program, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Moratorium Advocates, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Narcotic Addiction, 1964-1966 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Narcotic Addiction - Confronting the Realities, 1967 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Nassau County Correctional Center, 1972-1983 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - National Conference on Correctional Policy, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - National Conference on Corrections, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - National Council of Churches, 1970-1972 (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - National Council on Crime and Delinquency, 1962-1982 (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - National Council on Crime and Delinquency, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - National Institute of Corrections, 1979-1984 (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - National Institute of Corrections, 1979-1984 (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - National Institute for Sentencing Alternatives, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - National Jail Association, 1962 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - National Moratorium on Prison Construction, 1982-1984 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - National Organizations, 1982-1987 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - National Prison Project, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - National Prisoner Statistics, 1961-1975 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - National Prisoner Statistics, 1976-1984 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - New Jersey, ca. 1985 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - New Jersey Association on Correction, 1974-1982 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - New Jersey Association on Correction, News and Views, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - New Jersey Corrections Quarterly, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - New York City - Alternative Programs, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - New York City Bar Association, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - New York City Bar Association - Council on Criminal Justice, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - New York City Bar Association - Special Committee, 1975-1976 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - New York City Board of Correction, 1977-1984 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - New York City Board of Correction, 1980-1983 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - New York City - Budget, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - New York City - Budget, 1984-1985 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - New York City - Budget, 1985-1986 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - New York City - Budget - Message of the Mayor, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - New York City - Budget Summary - Fiscal Year 1985 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - New York City - Capital Costs, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - New York City - Citizens' Budget Commission, 1983-1985 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - New York City - Correctional Costs, 1976-1984 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - New York City - Costs, 1981-1984 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - New York City - Courts, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - New York City - Crime and Corrections, 1983-1985 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - New York City - Crime Statistics, 1984-1986 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - New York City - Criminal Justice System, 1977-1987 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - New York City Department of Correction, 1971-1980 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - New York City Department of Correction, 1979-1985 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - New York City Department of Correction - Reports, 1978-1982; 2 folders (Box 6, Folder 32-33)
  - New York City Department of Correction - Rehabilitation Services Coordinating Unit, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - New York City - Impact of President Reagan's Proposed Budget, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - New York City - Jail Expansion, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - New York City - Jail Overcrowding, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - New York City - Jail Overcrowding, Lynch Committee on, 1982-1983 (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - New York City - Jail Overcrowding, Lynch Committee on, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - New York City - Jails - Forced Release, 1983-1985 (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - New York City - Jails - 1986 Crisis, 1986-1987 (Box 6, Folder 41)
  - New York City - Jails - 1986 Crisis - Court Papers, 1986-1987 (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - New York City - Job Programs for Youths, 1985-1986 (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - New York City Office of Budget and Management, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 44)
  - New York City - Prison Programs Resources, ca. 1980 (Box 6, Folder 45)
  - New York City - Police, 1983-1985 (Box 6, Folder 46)
  - New York City - Probation, 1976-1984 (Box 6, Folder 47)
  - New York City - Report - Pretrial Services, ca. 1975-1984 (Box 6, Folder 48)
  - New York City - Testimony, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 49)
  - New York City - Youth Programs, 1984-1985 (Box 6, Folder 50)
  - New York Coalition for Penal Reform, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - New York Family Planner, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - New York State - Alternatives to Incarceration, 1983-1986 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - New York State - Alternatives to Incarceration - Estimated Costs and Savings, ca. 1975 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - New York State - Alternatives to Incarceration Task Force, 1983-1984 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - New York State - Alternatives to Incarceration Task Force - Report, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - New York State Assembly - Puerto Rican/Hispanic Task Force Conference, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - New York State - Bail, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - New York State Bar Association - "BASIC" Grants, 1974-1975 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - New York State Bar Visitation Project, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - New York State - Budget - Corrections, Alternatives, 1984-1987 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - New York State - Budget - General, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - New York State Catholic Conference, 1983-1984 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - New York State Coalition for Criminal Justice, 1975-1984 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - New York State Commission of Correction-Site Visits, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - New York State Commission of Investigation, Annual Report, 1985; 1985-1986 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - New York State - Crime Rates, 1986-1987 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - New York State Communities' Aid Association, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - New York State - County Jails, 1981-1986 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - New York State - Cuomo, Mario, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - New York State Defenders Association Brochure, ca. 1980 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - New York State Department of Correctional Services, 1975-1984 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - New York State Department of Correctional Services - Fiscal Year 1988-89 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - New York State Department of Correctional Services - Reports, 1978-1982 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - New York State Department of Correctional Services - Reports, 1981-1983 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - New York State Department of Correctional Services - Reports, 1981-1984 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - New York State Department of Correctional Services - Division of Program Planning - Research and Evaluation - Reports, 1984-1986 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - New York State Developmental Disabilities Planning Council, 1984-1987 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - New York State Division for Youth Assistance Project, 1964-1974 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - New York State Division of Parole - Reports, 1980-1984 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - New York State Division of Probation - Sentencing Proposal, 1982-1983 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - New York State Division of Probation - Sentencing Proposal, 1983-1984 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - New York State - Governor's State of the State Address - Criminal Justice Section, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - New York State - Gubernatorial Candidates, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - New York State Law Enforcement Council, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - New York State Law Enforcement Council, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - New York State - Laws and Evaluations, 1975-1977 (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - New York State - Legislation - Mandatory Sentencing, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - New York State - Legislation - Prison Overcrowding, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - New York State - Legislative Breakfast, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - New York State - Legislative History - 1973 Amendment (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - New York State - Legislative Memoranda - Miscellaneous, 1975-1977 (Box 7, Folder 42)
  - New York State Legislature - Black and Puerto Rican Caucus, 1983-1985 (Box 7, Folder 43)
  - New York State - Mental Hygiene Law Summary, ca. 1980 (Box 7, Folder 44)
  - New York State Narcotic Addiction control Commission, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 45)
  - New York State Office of Mental Health - Forensic Unit, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 46)
  - New York State Office of Vocational Rehabilitation, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 47)
  - New York State Prisons, Classification of, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 48)
  - New York State Prisons - Expansion Programs - Overcrowding, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 49)
  - New York State Prisons - Rehabilitation Programs, 1973-1985 (Box 7, Folder 50)
  - New York State Prisons - Sex Offenders, 1983-1987 (Box 7, Folder 51)
  - New York State Probation and Parole Officers Association, Inc., 1976 (Box 7, Folder 52)
  - New York State - Parole Board, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 53)
  - New York State - Reform Groups, ca. 1980 (Box 7, Folder 54)
  - New York State Sentencing Guidelines Committee, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 55)
  - Neufeld, Muriel, ca. 1985 (Box 7, Folder 56)
  - News Bulletin, June and October 1984 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - News Bulletin, 1986 December 19 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - News Clippings - Miscellaneous, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - News Clippings - Miscellaneous, 1986-1987 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - News Clippings - Op-ed - Miscellaneous, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - News Clippings - Op-ed - Miscellaneous, 1987 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - News Update, Summer 1983 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - 1960 Golden Anniversary White House Conference on Children and Youth (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - On the City's Master Plan - Summary, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - 128th Annual Report of the CANY, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Origins of the Underclass, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Osborne Association, 1961-1983 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Osborne Association - Administration, 1983-1984 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Osborne Association - Architectural Plans and Contracts, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Osborne Association - Contributions, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Osborne Association - Correspondence (Special), 1984-1986 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Osborne Association - Dependent Care Assistance Plan, 1984-1985 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Osborne Association - Dependent Care Assistance Plan, 1984-1985 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Osborne Association - Family Works Programs, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Osborne Association - Fundraising, 1982-1985 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Osborne Association - General, 1984-1987 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Osborne Association - Live Call - In Program, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Osborne Association - Mission Statements, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Osborne Association - Miscellaneous, 1982-1984 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Osborne Association - General Support, 1986-1988 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Osborne Association - Mailings, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Osborne Association - Members, 1976-1988 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Osborne Association - Membership Renewal, 1986-1987 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Osborne Association - Newsletter, 1963-1983 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Osborne Association - Program, 1983-1984 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Osborne Association - Program Director Search, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Osborne Association - Project Hometown America, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - Osborne Association - Proposals and Programs, 1984-1987 (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - Osborne Association - Renewal Letter, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - Osborne Association - Renovation, 1983-1984 (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - Osborne Association - Student Recognition Day, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - Osborne Association - Year - End Tax-Saving Letter, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - Ossining Correctional Facility, ca. 1915-1984 (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - Other Organizations, 1984-1986 (Box 8, Folder 39)
  - Parole, 1979-1986 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Parole (Outside New York), 1972-1982 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Parole/Probation, 1984 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Parole/Probation - Correctional Intervention, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Parole - Reports, 1975-1980 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Parolees - M.A. Thesis, 1965 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Pascual, Bonifacio Ramos, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Patterson, Robert, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Pennsylvania, 1961-1975 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Plan for Court and Probation Services, 1968 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Pornography, 1969-1971 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Position Statement on Narcotics, 1964 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Press Kit, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Press Literature, 1983-1986 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Press Releases/News Clippings, 1986-1987 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - "Pretrial Diversion of Youthful Adults", 1982 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Pretrial Release and Misconduct, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Pretrial Release Programs, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Preventive Detention, 1981 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Prison Action News, 1971 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Prison, Alternatives to, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Prison, Alternatives to - Trial Judges Conference, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Prison and Jail Overcrowding in New York State, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Prison Bond Issue, 1981 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Prison Bond Campaign, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Prison Bonds/Taxes - Passed/Rejected, ca. 1980 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Prison Culture, 1966 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Prison Furloughs, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - Prison Industries, 1973-1984 (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Prison Industries, 1981-1984 (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - Prison/Jail Construction, 1983-1985 (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - Prison Libraries, 1971 (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - Prison Overcrowding, 1982-1985 (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - Prison Overworking Articles, 1981-1982 (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - Prison Population Data, 1975-1984 (Box 9, Folder 35)
  - Prison Population Management, Calculations for Estimated Savings from Implementation of, 1984 (Box 9, Folder 36)
  - Prison Population Management, Calculations for Estimated Savings from Implementation of, Undated (Box 9, Folder 37)
  - Prison Population Management, 1984 (Box 9, Folder 38)
  - Prison Population - Rates of Incarceration - Total Numbers - Racial Disparities, 1979-1987 (Box 9, Folder 39)
  - Prison Riots/Disturbances, News Clippings, 1983 (Box 9, Folder 40)
  - Prison Work - Programs, 1983-1984 (Box 9, Folder 41)
  - Prisoners' Aid Societies, 1970-1978 (Box 9, Folder 42)
  - Prisoners' Bill of Rights, Undated (Box 9, Folder 43)
  - Prisoners' Families, 1970-1982 (Box 9, Folder 44)
  - Prisoners on the Payroll, Undated (Box 9, Folder 45)
  - Prisons - Children, 1985-1986 (Box 9, Folder 46)
  - Prisons - Federal, 1985-1986 (Box 9, Folder 47)
  - Prisons - Other Countries, 1983-1984 (Box 9, Folder 48)
  - Prisons, Parole and probation - Changes over the Years, 1984 (Box 9, Folder 49)
  - Prisons - Private, 1984-1985 (Box 9, Folder 50)
  - Prisons - Private, 1984-1986 (Box 9, Folder 51)
  - Prisons Under the Capitalist System, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 52)
  - Probation, 1970-1982 (Box 9, Folder 53)
  - Probation, 1980-1987 (Box 9, Folder 54)
  - Probation, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 55)
  - Project on Correctional Legislation, 1972-1973 (Box 9, Folder 56)
  - Proposed New York Penal Law, 1964 (Box 9, Folder 57)
  - Prostitution, 1958-1970 (Box 9, Folder 58)
  - Protect Prisoners' Constitutional Rights, Report of the Goldman Panel to, 1971 (Box 9, Folder 59)
  - Psychological Power and Pathology of Imprisonment, 1971 (Box 9, Folder 60)
  - Public Affairs Report, 1971-1972 (Box 9, Folder 61)
  - Public Opinion Polls, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 62)
  - Public Relation, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 63)
  - Publications Received, 1972-1974; 2 folders (Box 9, Folder 64-65)
  - Quaker Committee on Social Rehabilitation, Inc., 1970-1972 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Race and Community Relations Service, 1983 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Racial Disparities, 1985 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Recidivism, 1984 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Recidivism, 1985-1987 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Recommendations to the 1970 Legislature (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Recommendations to the 1971 Legislature (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Recommendations to the 1972 Legislature (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Recommendations to the 1975 Legislature (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Rehabilitation, 1968-1973 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Rehabilitation of the National Capital Area, Bureau of, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Release from Custody and Dismissal from Prosecution, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Report on Subject of Prison Reform, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Report of the Committee on Institutions and Offender Services on 1974-75 Visits to NYC Correctional Institutes, 1974-1975 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Report on "Victimless Crimes" in New York State, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - "Rhetoric and Reality of Prison Reform", 1972 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Rights of Prisoners, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Riker's Island, News Clippings, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Riker's Island - Problems, News Clippings, 1971-1976 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Riker's Island - Problems, News Clippings, 1976-1977 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Riker's Island Revolt, News Clippings, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Robinson to Driver to Easter (Study of Development of Involuntary Intoxication), 1967 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Rochester Bureau of Municipal Research, Inc., 1964 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Rochester Bureau of Municipal Research, Inc., 1967-1972 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - "Role of Race in the American Criminal Justice System", 1982-1983 (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Roosevelt Hospital Annual Report, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Rothman, David - Articles, 1973 (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Roundtable Discussion on Criminal Sentencing, 1976-1977 (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - Runaway and Homeless Youth in New York City, 1984 (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - Saint Peter's Church, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Selective Incapacitation, 1982-1983; 2 folders (Box 10, Folder 31-32)
  - Selective Incapacitation, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - Sentencing, 1977-1983 (Box 10, Folder 34)
  - Sentencing - Determinate, 1979-1984 (Box 10, Folder 35)
  - Sentencing Guidelines, 1982-1983 (Box 10, Folder 36)
  - Sentencing Guidelines, 1984-1986 (Box 10, Folder 37)
  - Sentencing Guidelines - U.S. Sentencing Commission, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 38)
  - Sentencing - Mandatory, 1977-1982 (Box 10, Folder 39)
  - Sentencing Policies, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 40)
  - Sentencing Practices, Procedures, and Consequences - Legal Aid Society Report, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 41)
  - Sentencing Reform, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 42)
  - Sexual Abuse, Crimes, Offenders, and Programs, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 43)
  - Sexual Issues, 1965-1972 (Box 10, Folder 44)
  - Short-term Adolescent Resident Training Center, 1962 (Box 10, Folder 45)
  - Short-term Detention - Official Reports, 1982-1983 (Box 10, Folder 46)
  - Should Alcoholics Be Absolved from Criminal Responsibility?, 1967 (Box 10, Folder 47)
  - Should Narcotics Be Prescribed to Addicts? No!, 1967 (Box 10, Folder 48)
  - Should the State Regulate Morality?, 1968 (Box 10, Folder 49)
  - Singer/Graflex Vocational Evaluation System, 1971-1972 (Box 10, Folder 50)
  - "Social Policy and the Future of Criminal Justice", 1988 (Box 10, Folder 51)
  - Socio-economic Causes of Crime, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 52)
  - Some Observations on the Sociological Aspect of Narcotics Addiction, 1961 (Box 10, Folder 53)
  - South Forty Corporation, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 54)
  - Speakers' Bureau, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 55)
  - State Correctional Systems, 1961 (Box 10, Folder 56)
  - State of the Prisons - CANY Report, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 57)
  - State Prison Overcrowding: Parole and Good Time Proposals, 1983 (Box 10, Folder 58)
  - State Prison Overcrowding: Blue Ribbon Panel, 1983 (Box 10, Folder 59)
  - State Prison Overcrowding: Proposed Legislation, 1983-1984 (Box 10, Folder 60)
  - Stay'n Out, ca. 1980 (Box 10, Folder 61)
  - Strategy Memos to Board of Directors, 1987-1988 (Box 10, Folder 62)
  - Suicide in Prisons, 1969-1970 (Box 10, Folder 63)
  - Suicide Prevention: Officer's Handbook, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 64)
  - Survey of a Representative Sample of Addicts Prescribed Heroin, 1970 (Box 10, Folder 65)
  - Testimony for City Council on Bill No. 721, 1968 (Box 10, Folder 66)
  - Texas, 1985-1987 (Box 10, Folder 67)
  - Therapeutic Abortions, 1967 (Box 10, Folder 68)
  - Toward a Crime Prevention Strategy, 1985 (Box 10, Folder 69)
  - Training Programs - General, 1966-1971 (Box 10, Folder 70)
  - Training Schools, 1970-1971 (Box 10, Folder 71)
  - Tri-State Consumers and Trade News, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 72)
  - U.N. Advisory Committee of NGO's to Social Defense, 1972-1973 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - U.S. Department of Justice - Bureau of Prisons, 1960-1972 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - U.S. Department of Justice - Crime, 1983-1984 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - U.S. Department of Justice - Law Enforcement Assistance Administration, 1965-1978 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - U.S. Supreme Court - Chronic Alcoholism and the 8th and 14th Amendments, 1965 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - U.S. Supreme Court - Prison-related Cases, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Urban League News, 1971-1973 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Veatch Program, 1982-1985 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Vera Institute of Justice, 1986 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Vera Institute of Justice - Community Service, 1981-1985 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Vermont Department of Corrections - Newsletters, 1971-1973 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Vesey Street Letter, 1972-1976 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - VISTA Riker's Island Project, ca. 1975 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Victim Compensation, 1965 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Victimless Crime, 1971-1972 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Victims of Crime, 1981-1982 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - VISTO Report - "Summary of Movement and Activities of Volunteers and Probationers, April-June 1970" (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Vocational Foundation, Inc., 1971 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Voluntary Correctional Service Agencies, Undated (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Volunteers, 1971-1972 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Volunteers in Probation Conference, April 1972, 1971-1972 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Von Hirsch, Andrew - Articles, 1979-1983 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Voters Against the Prison Construction Bond, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Westchester County, Action Plan to the Final Report of the Task Force on Corrections Overcrowding, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Westchester County Department of Community Mental Health, Annual Report, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Westchester County Department of Community Mental Health, Survey of Inpatient Care, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Westchester County - Directory of Community Mental Health Services, 1986 (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Westchester County Task Force on Corrections Overcrowding, Final Report, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - What Is Your Jail Like?, 1964 (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - What Prisons Do to People, 1985 (Box 11, Folder 30)